Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXVIII is arranged in 61 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXVIII. FINANCIAL ASSISTANCE
  - Sub-Series 387-0. Financial Assistance
    - System Boards of Adjustment. General, 1931 (Box 527, Folder 26)
    - System Boards of Adjustment. General, 1925-1926 (Box 527, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 387-2. Financial Assistance
    - Eastern Federation of General Chairmen, 1927 (Box 527, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 387-3. Financial Assistance
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1934 (Box 527, Folder 29)
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1932 (Box 527, Folder 30)
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1931 (Box 527, Folder 31)
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1929-1930 (Box 527, Folder 32)
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 527, Folder 33)
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 527, Folder 34)
    - Union Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1925-1926 (Box 527, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 387-4. Financial Assistance
    - Oregon Short Line System Board of Adjustment, 1925 (Box 527, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 387-5. Financial Assistance
    - O.W.R.& N. System Board of Adjustment, 1926 (Box 527, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 387-6. Financial Assistance
    - New England System Board of Adjustment, 1923 (Box 527, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 387-7. Financial Assistance
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1926 (Box 527, Folder 39)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1930 (Box 527, Folder 40)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis System Board of Adjustment, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 387-8. Financial Assistance
    - New York, Ontario, and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 387-9. Financial Assistance
    - Pere Marquette System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1933 (Box 528, Folder 3)
    - Pere Marquette System Board of Adjustment, 1931 (Box 528, Folder 4)
    - Pere Marquette System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 387-10. Financial Assistance
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 387-11. Financial Assistance
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1932-1936 (Box 528, Folder 8)
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1926-1931 (Box 528, Folder 9)
    - South Atlantic Department District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1938 (Box 528, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 387-12. Financial Assistance
    - Southeastern District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1932 (Box 528, Folder 11)
    - Southeastern District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1928-1929 (Box 528, Folder 12)
    - Southeastern District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1926-1927 (Box 528, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 387-13. Financial Assistance
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1936 (Box 528, Folder 14)
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1929 (Box 528, Folder 15)
    - St. Louis Southwestern System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1927 (Box 528, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 387-14. Financial Assistance
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1936-1937 (Box 528, Folder 17)
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1929 (Box 528, Folder 18)
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1927 (Box 528, Folder 19)
    - Texas and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1926 (Box 528, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 387-15. Financial Assistance
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1938 (Box 528, Folder 21)
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1931 (Box 528, Folder 22)
    - Kansas City Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1926-1927 (Box 528, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 387-16. Financial Assistance
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 24)
    - Great Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1926 (Box 528, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 387-17. Financial Assistance
    - New York Central Lines West System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1938 (Box 528, Folder 26)
    - New York Central Lines West System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 387-18. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago and Alton System Board of Adjustment, 1931 (Box 528, Folder 28)
    - Chicago and Alton System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1929 (Box 528, Folder 29)
    - Chicago and Alton System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 387-19. Financial Assistance
    - Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1935 (Box 528, Folder 31)
    - Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1929 (Box 528, Folder 32)
    - Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 387-20. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville System Board of Adjustment, 1943 (Box 528, Folder 34)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville System Board of Adjustment, 1934 (Box 528, Folder 35)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 387-21. Financial Assistance
    - Mobile and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1936 (Box 528, Folder 37)
    - Mobile and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 387-22. Financial Assistance
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, Southern Pacific Railroad, 1935-1937 (Box 528, Folder 39)
    - Texas and Louisiana District Board of Adjustment, Southern Pacific Railroad, 1927-1928 (Box 528, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 387-23. Financial Assistance
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac System Board of Adjustment, 1939-1940 (Box 528, Folder 41)
    - Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 387-24. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago and Western Lakes District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 387-25. Financial Assistance
    - Nickel Plate System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1929 (Box 528, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 387-26. Financial Assistance
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1936 (Box 528, Folder 45)
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1932 (Box 528, Folder 46)
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1931 (Box 528, Folder 47)
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 48)
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 49)
    - Hocking Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1927 (Box 528, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 387-27. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1941 (Box 528, Folder 51)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1931 (Box 528, Folder 52)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1930 (Box 528, Folder 53)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 387-28. Financial Assistance
    - Canadian Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1934-1942 (Box 528, Folder 55)
    - Canadian Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1932 (Box 528, Folder 56)
    - Canadian Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 57)
    - Canadian Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 387-29. Financial Assistance
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 387-30. Financial Assistance
    - Southern Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 387-31. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1933 (Box 528, Folder 61)
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 387-32. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1928 (Box 528, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 387-33. Financial Assistance
    - Soo Line System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1930 (Box 528, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 387-34. Financial Assistance
    - Pennsylvania Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1928-1929 (Box 528, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 387-35. Financial Assistance
    - Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 387-36. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago Great Western System Board of Adjustment, 1932 (Box 528, Folder 67)
    - Chicago Great Western System Board of Adjustment, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 387-37. Financial Assistance
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, Pacific Division System Board of Adjustment, 1937 (Box 528, Folder 69)
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, Pacific Division System Board of Adjustment, 1930 (Box 528, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 387-38. Financial Assistance
    - Norfolk and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1930 (Box 528, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 387-39. Financial Assistance
    - Northern District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1930 (Box 528, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 387-40. Financial Assistance
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Northern System Board of Adjustment, 1930 (Box 528, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 387-41. Financial Assistance
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1931 (Box 528, Folder 73)
    - Northern Pacific System Board of Adjustment, 1932 (Box 528, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 387-42. Financial Assistance
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, and St. Paul System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1936 (Box 528, Folder 75)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, and St. Paul System Board of Adjustment, 1932 (Box 528, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 387-43. Financial Assistance
    - Denver and Rio Grande Western System Board of Adjustment, 1932-1942 (Box 528, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 387-44. Financial Assistance
    - New York District Board of Adjustment, Express Division, 1933 (Box 528, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 387-45. Financial Assistance
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford System Board of Adjustment, 1933-1934 (Box 528, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 387-46. Financial Assistance
    - Chesapeake and Ohio System Board of Adjustment, 1935-1937 (Box 528, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 387-47. Financial Assistance
    - Kansas City Terminal System Board of Adjustment, 1936 (Box 528, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 387-48. Financial Assistance
    - Canadian National Express System Board of Adjustment, 1936 (Box 528, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 387-50. Financial Assistance
    - Central Vermont System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1938 (Box 528, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 387-51. Financial Assistance
    - Louisiana and Arkansas System Board of Adjustment, 1937 (Box 528, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 387-52. Financial Assistance
    - Florida East Coast System Board of Adjustment, 1937-1940 (Box 528, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 387-53. Financial Assistance
    - Rutland Railroad System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1939 (Box 528, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 387-54. Financial Assistance
    - Colorado and Southern System Board of Adjustment, 1938-1939 (Box 528, Folder 87)
  - Sub-Series 387-55. Financial Assistance
    - Lehigh Valley System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 528, Folder 88)
  - Sub-Series 387-56. Financial Assistance
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie System Board of Adjustment, 1939 (Box 528, Folder 89)
  - Sub-Series 387-57. Financial Assistance
    - Delaware and Hudson System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1941 (Box 528, Folder 90)
  - Sub-Series 387-58. Financial Assistance
    - Newfoundland Railway System Board of Adjustment, 1940-1941 (Box 528, Folder 91)
  - Sub-Series 387-59. Financial Assistance
    - Norfolk and Western System Board of Adjustment, 1941 (Box 528, Folder 92)
  - Sub-Series 387-60. Financial Assistance
    - Frisco System Board of Adjustment, 1941 (Box 528, Folder 93)
  - Sub-Series 387-61. Financial Assistance
    - Braniff Airways System Board of Adjustment, 1950-1954 (Box 528, Folder 94)
      December 1950-54.
  - Sub-Series 387-62. Financial Assistance
    - Western Airlines System Board of Adjustment, 1955 (Box 528, Folder 95)